Oh? You're here?
Did you sleep well?
Where were you?
We've been waiting for you.
- Good morning.
- Hello.
You're hungry, right?
It feels like I had
a bad dream.
[Lee Teuk]
[Shin Dong]
[DAWN]
[Johnny]
[Kim Yo Han]
[Ji Sung]
[Chapter.1]
[Walk the path that leads you to victory]
[EGYPT]
[Cairo]
It made me realize,
"Wow, I'm really in Egypt",
and honestly, it felt amazing.
The image of Egypt
in my head is like "Dune"?
The movie.
Pyramids, Sphinx, the capital Cairo...
I don't think I ever really
had a reason to visit Egypt before.
I always assumed
every city was just a desert.
All kinds of murals, Ramses...
That sort of vibe.
Honestly, it's pretty unfamiliar to me.
It feels like quite a mystical country.
[Setting off with hopes and imagination]
[A typical travel show]
[ALL or NOTHING]
[in EGYPT]
Well, hello.
[NCT127's Johnny
hops on the bus first]
[NCT DREAM's Ji Sung
follows after the NCT member]
Oh, hello!
It's starting already! Hello.
[A rather shy puppy, WEi's Yo Han]
[Bustling]
- The cellphone…
- Aha!
[From SUPER JUNIOR Lee Teuk,
who arrives with high expectations]
[DAWN, who enters
like a wandering lost soul]
Wow, the filming started already?
[To reliable Dong-geuri-dong-dong
SUPER JUNIOR's Shin Dong, everyone's on the bus!]
[The "ALL or NOTHING" crew is all here]
We just got here, and it's already chaotic
[So what kind of travel show
is "ALL or NOTHING"?]
[Time for a quick briefing]
[A land where 5,000 years
of history breathe and live]
[A Paradise Graced by Divine Blessings]
[EGYPT]
[Let's start with the member introductions]
[21 years of staying effortlessly cool]
[An outstanding prodigy]
[The names say it all]
[The all-rounders of SUPER JUNIOR]
[The K-POP textbook]
[Lee Teuk, Shin Dong]
[A genre unmatched by anyone else]
[Shining even in the darkest dawn]
[The irreplaceable solo artist, DAWN]
[Commanding presence on the stage]
[The hot guy from Chicago,
blessed with superior genes]
[The NCT 127 member
with perfect physique, Johnny]
[Here comes
the super big, super cute puppy]
[Perfect down to his soulful eyes]
[Visuals that tell a story, WEi's Yo Han]
[Baby hamster]
[Hidden behind that cute boy vibe]
[The powerful moves
of a main dancer]
[NCT DREAM's Youngest on Top, Ji Sung]
[So, why are WANGGEOZ here together?]
[The princes and the paupers
will be decided through a variety of games!]
Get it together, get it together!
[The game winners are]
It's here! It's here! It's here!
Come this way!
[Princes]
[The game losers are]
[Real paupers]
It's so cold.
I plan to be a prince, all the way.
[Want to be a prince?]
[A fierce competition is a given]
No way, this isn't right!
Why!
[Run, run, run, run, run, run, run!]
Ugh, I'm seriously so tired!
[Gestures full of brotherly love]
[Everyone takes the games very seriously]
[Sometimes you gotta
show your cute, playful side]
I… My run fast.
Oh my god. Th-ro-ro-ro-ro.
One more time. Pl... please…
[Why are they taking it this far…?]
So, this is what success tastes like.
[Princes get a feast fit for royalty]
[Luxurious accommodations provided]
Wow, this place is amazing!
[Paupers... fend for themselves]
I wanna go home…
[By the way, in Egypt]
It's freezing cold!
[There's no place to run or hide]
[Pauper life is the absolute worst]
It was truly the worst of the worst!
[Will it be a high-end luxury trip]
My name is Prince.
[Or a rock-bottom nightmare of a trip?]
Wow, I'm seriously a pauper.
[Unfolding all across Egypt]
[A survival trip at opposite extremes]
The first one…! 3 to the side!
I'll finish this in 5 minutes flat! Perfectly.
[Despair all you want]
I am…
I am a pauper!!!
[And fail miserably!]
[Only those who let it all go]
[Will become princes...]
Wow, Johnny is just…!
I am… I am a prince!
I'm a prince! Finally!
I am a prince!
Shin Dong, usually…
Are reality shows usually this hard?
[Epic mukbangs are a given!]
This is seriously delicious.
[Friends are made at the market]
[And visiting stunning places, like a travel show]
I feel so overpowered…
- Right?
- This is no joke.
- Why does it feel so unreal here?
- Right?
[Just watching this boosts happiness by 100%]
Nice one!
APT. APT. APT. APT.
[Please enjoy this romantic trip to Egypt with us]
- Why did we come to Egypt?
- I trust the production team.
[They head to their destination]
Right.
But isn't this lineup
of people kind of unusual?
- Of all time! It's a unique mix.
- A totally weird combo.
[The WANGGEOZ lineup is familiar, yet new]
I'm really curious why
they grouped us like this.
- Ji Sung, what year were you born?
- I was born in 2002.
Wow, that's like
a 30-year gap with Lee Teuk.
No!
We're exactly 20 years apart.
I started college in 2002.
[Wow…ancestor-status]
Wow…
- You're a World Cup baby.
- That's right.
You must hear
that all the time, right?
[What 2002 babies hear on repeat]
Yeah, all the time.
- Right? You hear it all the time?
- I hear it all the time.
Then, who's the youngest here?
Ji Sung?
- I think it's me.
- Were you born in 2000?
- I was born in 2002.
- 2002, and who's next?
[Yo Han, born in 1999]
I was born in 1999.
Yo Han, that's your birth name, right?
Yes, it's my birth name.
[DAWN, born in 1994]
I was born in 1994.
[Johnny, born in 1995]
Johnny was born in 1995.
The number suddenly shoots up.
[Jump! Shin Dong, born in 1985]
I was born in 1985.
It just suddenly shot up.
[Soaring like a semiconductor stock chart]
1985. Lee Teuk was 1983.
Oh, I'm so old!
I don't wanna be here!
Is this like an elimination show or something?
[Lee Teuk 44 - Shin Dong 42 -
DAWN 33 -Johnny 32 -Yo Han 28 -Ji Sung 25]
Hey, but what's with your eyes?
Oh, this…
[Ji Sung's eyes are red]
Because you're tired?
I cried so much
that the blood vessels popped.
- You cried so much? Yeah.
- Why?
Because you didn't wanna come to Egypt?
[Ji Sung's on a NCT DREAM tour]
After the concert…
[He cried during the encore stage]
Oh, then! That's understandable.
I found out for the first time.
[Thankfully, he says it doesn't hurt]
So the vessels burst from crying too much?
I just found out too.
It's everyone's
first time in Egypt, right?
- Totally my first time.
- That's right.
When I heard
we were going to Egypt,
[Interest #1: The Pyramids]
I thought it'd be worth it
to see the pyramids once.
[Interest #2: Soccer star Mohamed Salah]
Salah.
- Salah, the soccer player.
- Salah.
Right, Salah.
[Salah, a national hero hailed as the King of Egypt]
Is there a famous soccer player?
Yeah.
[Interest #3: Desserts]
I heard Egyptian desserts are famous.
- Desserts?
[Everyone's interested in different things]
Desserts.
- Koshari.
- What's that?
For Egypt, isn't it ROSÉ?
Egypt, Egypt…
[Doubting their own ears]
[Sorry]
[Oh my god...]
[Brace yourself]
He's gonna keep throwing out things like this.
[Holding back, since he's the oldest]
You gotta get used to it, okay?
- You have to get used to it. Sorry.
- But even now, the pyramids…
[The unresolved mystery
of how the pyramids were built]
- Isn't how they were built a mystery?
- Some stuff has come up…
- They're all just theories, though.
- Right?
- An enigma?
- It's all speculation. Theories.
Like, some say they
built them as long staircases.
Someone mentioned
it was a city submerged underwater…
That was me.
So they built it underwater?
So, "It used to be
a city submerged underwater."
I always thought giants built them.
Giants?
Seo Jang Hoon?
[He is a giant]
You mean Jang Hoon?
Did Jang Hoon build it?
How giant does the giant have to be?
- Like Choi Hong Man?
[Totally his vibe]
Seo… Jang Hoon…
[Determined]
Didn't they find giant skeletons or something?
It seems like DAWN
watches a lot of fake news.
[Hehe]
Try looking it up.
Where do you get your news?
- But I really saw the photos!
- Really?
[He swears]
Giants...
Please search for
"Pyramids, giants."
[Shin Dong] How come the buildings
all look the same, no matter how far we go?
They look really interesting.
- Even the colors are all the same.
- Yeah.
[Observation mode]
The colors are all kind of the same.
- Did they match the tone on purpose?
- Are they building it with the dirt here?
[Because of the desert sandstorms,
most buildings in Cairo are beige-toned]
Everything's beige,
because there's a lot of sand.
- That's a redevelopment zone over there.
- Huh? What's this place?
Is this some kind of historic site?
- Oh, it's being redeveloped?
- A redevelopment zone, right?
Oh, it's a redevelopment zone?
- Isn't that the redevelopment area over there?
- Oh, this is the redevelopment zone?
Hey! Then you should've bought land!
- You should've bought it all!
- Did they clear everything out?
This must be a movie set.
Is "Arabian Nights" from Egypt?
[Not sure why, but everyone starts laughing]
[Suddenly, his host instincts kick in]
Honestly, if we talk about Egypt
right now, we don't really know much.
[Listening]
So as we travel,
we'll get to know and learn
more about Egypt.
And we'll share about Egypt
with everyone watching this!
- That's right.
- Oh, it's that kind of broadcast?
[Lee Teuk jumped to his own conclusion]
It's not?
I've only done shows like that.
Lee Teuk, the script… Where is your script?
I've only done that kind of show.
[Can't help but keep laughing for some reason]
Isn't this an Egypt product placement?
It's like…
But where are we headed?
Yeah, where are we going?
We know nothing.
Oh! Over there!
- Oh! Over there!
- Where?
- Over there!
- Oh, wow!
- Oh, the pyramids!
- There!
On the right?
- Over there!
- Whoa, amazing!
[Pyramids in sight!]
What? That…
[Johnny wants to see the pyramids too...]
That's how big it is? On the right?
- Over there!
- Whoa, amazing!
[Kept mirroring Shin Dong's line of movement]
- That's how big it is?
- The pyramid! The pyramid!
[This is seriously surreal!]
Wow!
- Wow, I just got chills.
- It's really huge.
Oh, I'm suddenly wide awake!
[Can't believe I'm seeing such a grand
and huge monument with my own eyes…!]
It's really huge.
Right next to the city.
[The pyramids are
right next to the city!]
Wow…
I thought
we'd see them on the last day.
But we saw them from the start,
so it was so surprising and amazing.
[For his personal collection]
When Lee Teuk said,
"Look over there," I looked to the right.
And the pyramids were huge!
Wow, they're that big?!
I honestly got goosebumps.
I was like "Wow".
It's seriously massive!
Oh, but, seeing it up close like this,
[Finally get why it's a wonder of the world]
I understand why people wonder about it.
Right? How did they even build that?
The height is…
- If we go close by, it'll be super high.
- They built a whole mountain.
[For some reason, it feels like a reward]
It's really tall.
Just how tall is it, though?
Is it as tall as Namsan Tower?
Wow! Oh, there are two!
- No, there's more.
- There are three of them.
- Oh, there's a tiny one over there, too.
- There are so many.
[Whispering]
This is seriously amazing.
Isn't it one of the Three Wonders of the World?
Isn't it the Seven Wonders of the World?
- Seven…
- Oh, it's seven?
Wow, that list keeps growing
[LOL]
The list keeps growing…!
Oh, we're getting closer!
[Everything's amazing]
Those camels are really tall.
Wait, can the bus
actually get this close?
Wow.
We're literally right beside it!
[Getting closer to the pyramids]
[Pure wonder]
Does it feel like we're really in Egypt now?
Johnny, what do you think?
It feels like we're here!
- It feels like we are?
- Yes.
[The more you look, the more in awe you are]
Everyone, look to your right.
It's the pyramids.
- Everyone, we're in Egypt right now.
- Wait a sec.
This looks like Cairo,
but it's not actually Cairo.
[This is the view just from the bus]
It's Giza, Giza, Giza.
Look to the left, there's a café.
[A shot of the pyramids by Ji Sung]
They built this 4,600 years ago?
Whoa, pyramids!
Is the café in front
of the pyramids different?
Let's check it out.
[First meetup spot]
[A café with a pyramid view]
[Getting off with excitement]
Let's go!
- Wow!
I think it feels hotter
next to the pyramids.
What's this?
Wow!
- How many floors do you think that is?
- So fascinating.
The six of us look cool,
all dressed up and walking over.
It kinda feels like we're kings.
[Our WANGGEOZ makes us proud,
no matter where they go]
"The Pyramids of Giza".
It feels so surreal that
the pyramids are actually right there.
[The Great Pyramid of Khufu
stands tall amidst Giza's sandy winds]
[Beneath the blazing desert sun]
[The triangular giants that have
braved sandstorms for thousands of years]
[The three pyramids of the Giza Plateau]
[The tombs of King Khufu,
King Khafre, and King Menkaure]
[One can feel the mighty legacy
of a dynasty dreaming of eternity]
[The Sphinx, the guardian of the pyramids]
[A massive statue carved
from a whole mountain rock]
[The grandeur of the Great Sphinx]
[In the place where myths breathe,
"ALL or NOTHING" begins its first journey]
What's up with him?
[Everyone, let's snap
some memories before we go]
What's he doing?
[Take a photo of Johnny]
You can take a photo of me.
Lee Teuk, come here.
Let's take a photo together.
Alright.
[Shin Dong and Lee Teuk]
Oh, it came out great!
[Can't resist a selfie
in front of the pyramids]
[The pyramid's right here with Ji Sung]
[Not taking a picture of this
would be a crime]
[Shining even brighter
in front of the pyramids]
[The handsome faces of
our soon-to-be princes and paupers]
[Looking sharp, Johnny]
[Let's soak up the good energy here
in the land of living myths]
[We are "ALL or NOTHING"]
Don't you think
the sun is really strong in Egypt?
[Egypt, where the desert sun blazes down]
It's super strong, it's crazy.
I heard using sunscreen
protects your skin really well.
But I hate that sticky feeling.
It's super light, and keeps your skin hydrated.
It's really light.
[Sunscreen is a must during this Egypt trip!]
It comes out like water.
So light and moisturizing!
It's so nice!
[His English pronunciation boosts credibility]
It feels light.
Your English pronunciation is great.
How does it feel?
Totally light! Not sticky at all.
Can heavy guys use this?
- Maybe you'll feel lighter.
- Shin Dong, you'll feel lighter!
[Getting lighter]
I feel like I'm getting lighter!
Just holding it makes me feel lighter.
[Johnny's skin is precious]
I should take one.
Alright, everyone. Welcome to Egypt.
But isn't it starting
to really hit you now?
Since we're in front of the pyramids.
Honestly, I had a dopamine rush
as soon as I saw the pyramids.
- Yeah, yeah.
- I know, right?
- Here…
- You must be an F-type. Are you an F-type?
[A totally capital T]
I'm a total T-type.
Oh really? Even T-types are moved by this?
As you all know,
we're here together for a travel show.
To fully experience this trip,
you just have to enjoy
the missions and the games
that we prepared.
- Nothing's free.
- Oh, so there are missions?
No freebies.
Depending on the results,
as you know,
some will get
to live it up in luxury.
[Some will lose it all on this trip]
And those who lose
will lose absolutely everything.
But if we become paupers,
just how much will we be losing?
[Half worried, half curious]
I'm curious.
In a way, it could be romantic, right?
Do you usually think of those things as romantic?
Like, for example…
[Romanticize mode on]
Pitching tents and sleeping right by the pyramids.
[Isn't that romantic?]
It's not bad to try it once.
Once in a lifetime…!
[Selfless mode at full power]
Then you can do it instead.
[No way]
But, like, we should still play the games.
The missions will be done as 3 vs 3,
[Missions will be played as 3 vs 3,
6 vs 0, or a free-for-all]
a free-for-all, or 6 vs 0.
- 6 vs 0.
- What's 6 vs 0?
[6 vs 0: Everyone succeeds or everyone fails]
We team up together and go against the staff.
Honestly, I think
rather than a 3 vs 3 or a 1 vs 1,
a 6 vs 0 will be even more stressful.
- A free-for-all might be better.
- I'm bad at games, so bad.
Then can we decide that ourselves?
Like, will it be 1 vs 1 or 3 vs 3?
Sometimes, we'll assign the teams,
and other times,
we'll give you time to decide on your own.
Then, how about for the first game,
we start together as a group.
Let's go with 6 vs 0.
Oh? We actually have something prepared.
Didn't you say
you'd give us time to decide?
Come on, Lee Teuk.
I thought we were going with 6 vs 0.
I don't vibe well here. I'm gonna leave!
For today, we'll reveal
the first game we've prepared.
- Oh?
- Okay.
I'm getting nervous.
To experience local Egyptian cuisine,
[Pharaoh's Table]
this is the Pharaoh's Table.
- Pharaoh's Table.
- Are we guessing the prices?
Shin Dong's already guessing.
I don't wanna be a pauper!
I've lived that life
since I was a kid!
Sorry, but Shin Dong
and I have that pauper instinct.
Starting in the order of
appetizers, seafood, meats, and dessert,
[A full-course dining mission!]
we've got a full-course meal prepared for you.
- Oh.
- Wow.
- We're gonna eat that?
- That's the mission?
We have to eat everything!
You're not sitting down
in one place for the whole full-course meal.
We have to move around?
[1 Appetizer → Move]
In order of the courses,
[2 Seafood → Move]
you'll go around
[3 Meat → Move]
to the restaurants
[4 Dessert → Finish]
we reserved,
and the team that arrives first wins.
[Dopamine's kicking in]
Wow! Hold up!
[We're doing such a huge mission from the start?]
A mission that big already?
Here?
[Pharaoh's Table]
[Hit up selected restaurants
and enjoy Cairo's best food]
[The team that eats first,
up to the last dessert, becomes princes]
[Pharaoh's Table rules]
[Full-course dining order]
[Appetizer → Seafood → Meat → Dessert]
[Each team gets its own transport]
[There are 7 restaurants marked on the map]
Two places for appetizers.
Two places for seafood.
Two places for meat, and lastly,
the final meetup
spot is a dessert café.
[Appetizer]
We're not going to
[Seafood]
reveal where
[Meat]
what restaurant is where just yet.
[Seafood A VS Seafood B]
[Listen to a "keyword" and pick
one of the two restaurants for each course!]
[A race where the distance
and menu depend on luck and intuition]
So, we don't even know
the names of the restaurants?
No names, no locations.
We're only going
to give you keywords.
[A race based on luck]
[The keyword choices decide everything]
You've seen this
on social media lately, right?
There's a game where
you clear the closest cups first
or clear the farthest cups first.
The person who clears
the farthest cups first always wins.
- That's right.
- Let's go for the farthest spots first.
[So here's the deal,
let's hit up the farthest spots first!]
[Explaining again]
We still don't know which place is where.
Ugh, this game is making my head spin!
We just have to eat well
and finish the chosen courses in order.
[Brainy Shin Dong totally gets it]
Right, since there are two of each,
one team goes this way,
the other team goes that way.
Okay, then first…
Let's talk about
who wants to eat meat
and who wants to eat seafood.
No, that's not it at all.
[Code Red. He doesn't get the rules,
no matter how much we explain them]
- He still doesn't get the game.
- I understand it now.
- You got it?
- Lee Teuk, it's a course meal.
When the game starts,
the two teams can eat three dishes in order.
We're hitting up all the places
for meat, seafood, and appetizers.
- Right, right.
- But there's an A option and a B option for each.
[The star instructor explaining the rules]
We'll choose one. So, we'll keep splitting up.
So we decide whether to go to A or B?
For that, we'll choose teams
and head out for each mission.
The staff failed at this game.
[Speaking his mind]
That's just how I see it.
But the problem is, we don't know
which is dessert, meat, or seafood here.
Oh!
Because there's a bit
of distance between them.
Oh!!
You're all playing
the same game I am, right?
Yo Han is clueless.
Stop pretending you know!
- I have a rough idea.
- Rough? No, you don't have a rough idea.
Then explain it.
So you're saying we start
by clearing the farthest cups first.
You and I are pretty much
on the same page right now.
So which cup are we hitting first?
[Let me think...]
Johnny's cup.
[Crinkle]
I was shocked when Yo Han suddenly said
we should clear the farthest cup first.
But why is everyone
struggling to understand the rules?
The Pharaoh's Table will
[The Pharaoh's Table is a 3 vs 3 showdown]
take place as a 3 vs 3 battle.
Since it's the first mission,
we went ahead and picked the teams ourselves.
As long as it's not like this…
Like, 3 vs 3 like this…
- Right now, we're too…
- What? What?
[Reason: All three of them are too gentle]
The three of us are too gentle and soft.
Let's go, let's go!
It's okay, as long as
the SUPER JUNIOR members aren't together.
We'll fight if we're together.
We kept it simple and split the teams
- according to the dishes.
- Oh, yes.
Now, Lee Teuk and Shin Dong,
please swap seats.
- Huh?
- Like this?
Oh, like this?
- Oh, we're in trouble.
- Wait, wait a second.
[Lee Teuk, Johnny, Ji Sung]
Oh, we're in trouble. Oh, Johnny…!
[Don't come this way, Lee Teuk]
Lee Teuk!
What? What trouble!
[Frantic waving x127]
Lee Teuk, not this side!
Hey, why are we in trouble?
How can you give me duds?
[Sudden jump]
Duds? What do you mean by "duds," Shin Dong?
[I have no faith in these two]
What am I supposed to do with two duds?
[His honest truth]
I honestly just wanted to send Ji Sung over.
[A mission where being slim works against you]
I had a feeling, Johnny.
Johnny, I really did.
Johnny looks like he eats a lot, though.
[Eats enough to maintain his energy]
I eat just enough…
- Like what I see…
- I think he eats little.
You don't like
leaving food behind, right?
- Yeah, I hate leaving food.
- I really don't like it.
[Hamster tries his best to impress]
I'm in my prime these days.
You're in your prime? We're good.
But the mission might
not be to eat everything.
You have to finish everything.
[Must eat all the food
to move to the next restaurant]
I didn't understand the rules.
- I eat super fast.
- I can finish a burger under a minute.
I can eat two hamburgers.
[The person with the biggest disadvantage]
Oh, that's why they paired me up with DAWN!
I surprisingly eat well!
[Laughs]
Shin Dong, I really, probably…
If you eat as much as I do? You'll die…
Everyone's so nice, so…
[Pure soul]
"The member lineup doesn't matter."
That was the first thought I had.
Whoaaaaa!
[The hamster jumps
in panic as a bug flies by]
[That's not a bug]
It's just dust.
Legendary.
[Awkward hamster moment]
It was just dust…
I thought it was a bug…Wow.
[Kinda embarrassed
now that he thinks about it]
I wasn't happy with it.
It kind of felt like I had
two fragile kids stuck next to me.
We'll reveal the keyword
for the first appetizer restaurant.
[Revealing the keyword
for the first "Appetizer" restaurant]
Once each team selects,
we'll mark it on the map for you.
[After choosing,
the locations will be revealed on a map]
Now, the first keyword for
the appetizer restaurant is…
A.
[A = A flavorful national dish]
A flavorful national dish.
- F.N.D!
- A flavorful national dish!
F.N.D!
B.
- Healthy soul food.
- H.S!
[B = Healthy soul food]
Healthy soul food.
[Exchanging glances]
Isn't it "A"?
- Definitely!
- Definitely "A".
[Both teams quickly lean towards A]
That side will pick "A" too.
It's totally like spicy stir-fried pork.
"B," "B."
[Eyes full of confidence]
Why, Shin Dong?
You wanna eat fast, right?
Something healthy means smaller portions.
[Team meeting time]
Please discuss and choose.
National dishes come in huge portions.
- Oh, you're right.
- Yeah.
[Successfully convinced]
It has to be large since it's a national dish
[Egypt's staple food is]
And, what's the national dish here?
[Meat & bread, so bound to get full fast]
It's meat and bread.
I'm Korean, so I picked the national dish.
But it's not our national dish…?
It's this nation's.
[Kim Yo Han (Korean)]
Right, we're in Egypt.
[Currently Egyptian]
Then, going with healthy food…
I had a bit of faith in Yo Han, but…
He's kind of a goofball, too… So…
This isn't gonna be easy either…
That's what I was thinking.
Honestly, in places like this,
it's better to pick
something you're not craving.
So, I'm going with
the one I'm not feeling.
[Blind faith in the leader 1]
I trust your gut feeling.
- Then, I'll also trust you.
- Then, just trust me for the first one.
Trust me, and if I'm wrong…
For the next one, I'll trust you guys.
For games like this... honestly,
you gotta eat fast
and move on quickly.
So there are two strategies!
[1. Go nearby]
First, go to the closest spot.
[2. Go for smaller portions]
Second, choose the place with less food.
But,
[1. Not sure which spot is closest]
if you don't know the exact location,
then when choosing between the two,
you have to pick the one
that seems to have less food.
[Meanwhile, Team Lee Teuk is deep in debate]
Look, healthy food could actually be pizza.
- Pizza's fast.
- Right.
Pizza's fast.
But "healthy" sounds fancy,
so it might be served slowly.
[Team Lee Teuk's logic #2]
But, in a way,
[The overall location matters more]
The first choice is based on luck,
because we have no clue where to go.
We've made up our minds.
- Should we say it first, then?
- Hold on, hold on.
What do we do now?
But honestly speaking,
let's just choose romance…
[Romance accepted]
That's really thrilling.
And, even if it's just one meal!
- Let's enjoy it!
- Enjoy it!
If you enjoy your food,
then it's what?
[Suddenly, enjoying food means zero calories]
It's zero calories.
For the first one,
we have to go for the shortest distance.
Since the goal is to win the game,
we were hoping the restaurants we picked
would all be close to each other…
I think we were
[Chasing romance while holding onto hope]
half excited and half nervous.
[Team Lee Teuk chooses first]
We're here in Egypt, right?
So we're gonna try
the national dish of Egypt.
Two, three!
"A"!
Hey, you have to do it with me…
You didn't even tell them to.
[Unfair]
Like, you have to go with your gut!
We'll go with the national dish of Egypt.
[Trying again]
One, two, three!
"A"!
[Then, what will Team Shin Dong pick?]
Now, Team Shin Dong.
For us,
we sort of want to eat something light
- for the first dish.
- Right, right.
And it seems that the word
"healthy" stood out for us.
So we made our choice.
Our team picks…!
[Team Shin Dong picks B: Healthy soul food]
"B"!
[Revealing the first appetizer restaurant]
We'll reveal the locations of each restaurant.
This is what's important.
Let's take a look!
- Oh!
- It doesn't matter.
- I'm trusting Johnny on this.
- It's literally right next door.
Oh, okay, okay.
[A. A flavorful national dish]
[B. Healthy soul food]
Oh, then this spot would be bad.
[The problematic spots]
On both sides.
- They gave us the ones in the middle on purpose.
- At least, we'll get there a little faster.
Before you head out…!
It'd be a shame to just end it here,
so we prepared a mini-game!
- Okay.
- Alright.
Is it to depart first?
Or to pick our car?
[The most important thing in a racing game]
When you're in a racing game,
what matters most
to beat your opponent?
- Items.
Banana peels.
We'll play a game to get items!
[A game to acquire special items]
Oh!
Oh, there's something like this?
If it's an item, is it like a digestive aid?
[Wild guess]
Or, like, a 5-minute wait in the car?
Oh, could it be something like that?
That would be so funny.
[Lose one serving of our food?]
Or maybe lose one serving.
[Add a serving to the other team!]
Or like add another serving.
Add a serving to the other team.
[Getting a crazy look in his eyes for some reason]
While you're eating, "What's this?"
"The other team ordered it for you."
"They've used an item."
We'll begin the mini-game to acquire items.
It's titled: "The Guardian of the Pyramid".
You're going for a Sphinx vibe.
You will all become the Sphinx yourselves
and guard the pyramid.
- Guard what?
- No way…
Is it like standing
in front of it for as long as possible?
From each team, one person will play.
And like the Sphinx,
the person who holds
a plank the longest…
[Seven Wonders of the World]
[The pyramids]
[The Sphinx, the guardian who watches in front]
[Embody the Sphinx
and outlast your opponent!]
[A plank in this heat?]
[Variety shows are tough these days...]
It's 34 degrees Celsius here...
Oh, this is the absolute worst for me.
[Both teams wrestle with worry and confidence]
This is good. We're in a good spot.
- It's not bad at all.
- Not bad at all. It's so great.
Should we explain the items now?
[What items will they get?]
Or later…
Just give us a quick teaser.
[Curious]
I gotta say
I was impressed
by Lee Teuk's intuition earlier.
It's one of the things he mentioned.
- It is?
- Oh, really?
The first item is
"The gentleman over there sent it".
[First item]
[The gentleman over there sent it]
[While each person is eating a serving]
[An extra serving will be
added when the item is used]
We need to get that item,
no matter what.
- I might curse while eating.
- I know, right?
[Already worried]
The second item is
[Second item]
"One hand's just for support".
- This one is…
- Is it eating with one hand?
[Second item]
[One hand's just for support]
[If the item is used during a meal]
[You must eat with your hands
tied together like a three-legged race]
That item is seriously the worst
[Already uncomfortable just hearing it]
That's gonna be so uncomfortable.
Let me introduce the third item.
Played here in Egypt,
[Third item]
a traditional coin game.
[Is it the coin I know?]
Coin?
- Not that coin.
- Oh, you got me there.
[Could it be the coin-flipping?]
Coin-flipping?
- It's a coin-flipping game.
- Oh, like this, like this
[Yes, it's the coin flip game]
[Third item]
[Traditional coin game]
[If the item is used during the meal]
[You must flip 6 coins to resume eating]
[The first official game of "ALL or NOTHING"]
Then, we'll begin the plank battle
under the blazing sun.
["The Guardian of the Pyramid" will
determine the fate of the three items]
[Team Shin Dong's core strategy]
Here's the plan.
Let's toss the cards
we don't need first.
[And that is me]
So, I will be going first.
First, we have
Shin Dong and Ji Sung stepping up.
How much do you weigh?
- I'm 87 kg.
- 87 kg. And Ji Sung?
- I'm 64 kg.
- 64?
[An extreme wealth gap]
That's a 25 kg difference.
The current temperature is
nearing 37 degrees Celsius.
Please get ready, everyone.
[Flinching]
It's so hot just standing here. Wait.
This yoga mat's burning hot!
- This is way too hot!
- Wow, it's this hot.
[Heat so intense it's hard even to stand]
When you hear the whistle,
you must lift your knees.
[Ready for the Item Mission: Round 1]
Yes.
Ready.
[Bad posture right from the start]
You gotta lower your hips a bit.
[Soul shield]
It's because his butt is big.
- No, you really need to lower it.
- It's just the shape of it, the shape.
[Even if his hips are big, this posture is not it]
He's not a pyramid or anything.
His hips just shot up.
Don't laugh.
[Born with high hips]
I can't help it that my hips are high.
It's because my butt is big!
[Standing tall]
It's got nothing to do with size.
No, like, this is…
[A visibly clear height difference]
Ji Sung's is down here, but his butt is up there.
Are you a pyramid or what?
[Planking or building a landmark?]
How am I supposed to lower it more?
- I'm already trembling. Hold on…
- He's shaking.
Hold on, hold on.
[Already in a crisis, 30 seconds in]
- You're starting to feel it, right?
- Huh? Wait.
[Trembling]
Wait, is someone…
- Is someone calling me?
- No, there's no phone.
[Full-body vibration mode]
Am I getting a call? Why am I…
There's no call, no call.
- Meanwhile, Ji Sung is…
- Ji Sung's really good at this.
Ji Sung's kind of shaking.
[Steadily holding a perfect form]
Don't think about anything, Ji Sung.
I'm slipping! Hold on!
Ji Sung, the man with two hearts!
One minute, thirty seconds have passed.
[Round 1]
[Time elapsed: 1m 30s]
Shin Dong's posture keeps improving.
[When he started]
[After 1m 30s]
[His posture gets better over time]
Hey, your form got way better.
Hey, don't make me laugh!
[Barely on his tiptoes]
He's slipping! He's slipping!
Think of it as meditation.
Just relax.
Wait a minute, this…
Hey, I'm slipping way too much.
Wow…
[Ji Sung's feeling it too]
It's not Shin Dong slipping.
The mat is stretching.
This mat is stretching
way too much.
Right now…
- His entire body is trembling!
- Wait!
- Okay, trembling!
- Shin Dong, you've got this!
[Barely holding on with all their might]
- This isn't easy. - You can do this!
Will they be a prince or a pauper?
[As time goes by...]
[There seems to be no hope
for Team Shin Dong's throwaway card]
[Just as all hope was fading away]
- Ji Sung, you wanna give up?
- Shin Dong, why are you so good at this?
How about we just lose?
- Wanna play Rock-Paper-Scissors?
- Yeah.
How about we just lose?
- Shin Dong, wanna play Rock-Paper-Scissors?
- Yeah.
[Rock-Paper-Scissors at this timing…???]
Rock-Paper-Scissors!
[Ji Sung: Scissors]
[If Shin Dong wins,
the tables will completely turn!]
[Ji Sung wins]
Oh, c'mon.
[There was no miracle]
Okay! No, wait…!
[Confused]
It's not okay. Hold up.
[Team Lee Teuk acquires an item]
Team Lee Teuk wins.
[The aftermath of a 2-minute plank]
This is insane…The hands…!
[Round 1: Ji Sung wins]
Wow, this is no joke.
Flip the mat, flip the mat.
Can you film this?
There are sweat drops!
Seriously, wow.
[The traces of an intense battle]
Wow, for real...!
Guys, it's okay to lose. Got it?
We can just eat a lot, so it's fine.
Round 1 winner, Ji Sung!
Please pick your item
[The winner of each round picks the item]
Oh, so you pick an item every time you win.
[Thinking carefully]
What items were there?
Giving one more serving.
[Plank Mission Item]
The coin thing.
The coin flip.
- Tying one hand.
[This could affect the main game]
Tying one hand is definitely…
- One more?
- Yeah, one more.
[What will Team Lee Teuk pick?]
Go tell them, "Give one more serving."
One more serving.
"The gentleman over there sent it"!
"The gentleman over there sent it".
[The gentleman over there sent it]
- Wow, but you seriously did well.
- Nice.
It's okay. We'll just eat an extra serving.
[Sorry]
If that mission comes up, I'll eat it.
- We can just eat it.
- We can eat it together.
[Item Mission: Round 2]
This is a battle of the fit guys.
He used to be a Taekwondo athlete.
- That's right.
- Yes.
- Will it be Yo Han, the former athlete…
- The former athlete.
[Round 2 player:
Yo Han from Team Shin Dong]
[All-round sports idol]
Johnny's a basketball player.
A basketball player!
[Round 2 player:
Johnny from Team Lee Teuk]
It's a battle between basketball and Taekwondo!
If you go in that direction…!
[Pressure]
- If you go in that direction…
- We have to do it!
The Korean
[The Taekwondo athletes are watching]
Taekwondo community is watching!
The Korean basketball
community is watching!
[Korea]
The NBA is watching!
[Basketball rep VS Taekwondo rep]
The KBL is watching!
[Taekwondo is all about the core]
Taekwondo is known for core power.
[Basically, please win]
That's right. He'll definitely win this.
[Yo Han, former Taekwondo athlete]
[Johnny, all-round sports idol]
[Ace VS Ace]
Ready.
[Who will win Round 2?]
Johnny's posture is on point.
[Starting with steady postures]
I think these two will do it for a long time.
Seriously, these two
will be at it for a long time.
We can just go and come back.
[Razor-sharp postures
like the aces they are]
They're both good. Great forms.
[Perfectly synced like the Sphinx]
But this is really insane.
- Did you do it for about 2 minutes?
- Yeah, yeah, yeah.
After 2 minutes,
it was seriously so hard.
Oh, it's here, it's here!
[Is it a battle cry or a scream?]
It's a battle cry, definitely a battle cry!
Nice!
[Both players are wobbling]
Their hips are trembling.
- Oh, they're both shaking.
- Johnny's feeling it too.
[1 minute elapsed]
1 minute has passed.
- Wow!
- Shin Dong did really well earlier, then.
Yeah, it's hard to last a minute!
- Right.
- 1 minute is rough.
I thought, "I think I'm shaking right now."
Then I glanced over at Johnny,
[Twerking]
and he was twerking so hard.
I…
[I could feel Johnny swaying so much]
Amidst the swaying flowers,
- I could feel Johnny so much.
- Johnny is good.
- Guys who take pride in their fitness…
- That's right.
[When Johnny struggles, he twerks…]
get really competitive.
Wow, like that…
[Thrown off by this never-before-seen dance move]
Shaking like that…!
It seems like
he's shaking on purpose, right?
Shin Dong.
[This round]
I'm not gonna lose.
Nice.
Yo Han's going for it!
[Yo Han gains confidence after Johnny's twerk]
He's in the zone! He's in the zone!
This is the only thing you're good at.
Both of their ears are bright red.
If it's hard, don't hesitate to yell.
Nice!
You're good!
[The game drags on, as expected of an ace match]
Nice! Wow!
[Teasing]
Johnny is wobbling a lot.
Like full-on twerking level.
[Is Johnny unable to stop twerking]
I think Johnny's really struggling…
[Because of his fierce desire to win…?]
We literally just started filming
as soon as we arrived in Egypt today.
We flew for 25 hours.
Exactly. As soon as we got here,
- we prepared for this.
- We didn't eat anything.
[Heatwave + Long haul flight]
[Much more exhausting than usual]
Oh, Johnny's at his limit now.
[Our Johnny needs...]
[Some serious cheering...]
Johnny, remember
those tough trainee days of yours.
[Me, NCT 127's Johnny…]
[And my 8 years as a trainee?]
Remember those tough trainee days...
Johnny, Johnny!
Remember those
tough trainee days of yours.
[Energy drained just thinking about it]
Johnny, Johnny!
Johnny!
[I didn't mean any harm, Johnny]
[Straight to a victory celebration]
Good job! Good job, Yo Han Kim!
Nice! Show us! Show us!
[Recorded 3 minutes and 30 seconds]
That's right!
[Round 2: Yo Han wins]
Well done.
[Did his best, but unfortunately lost]
You did well, you did well.
- It's hard, right?
- It's hard.
[Picking the Round 2 item]
Wait, we need to pick the mission first.
- Oh, right.
- There's the hand-tying one.
[Remaining items]
There's the hand-tying one.
If we pick the hand-tying one,
this team will tie their hands, right?
- Yeah.
- I think the coin one will be easy.
- The hand-tying one, the hand-tying one.
- The coin one is…
Go with the wrist one.
We'll go with the hand-tying one.
- The hand-tying one.
- Yes.
[One hand's just for support]
Yes.
Nice, that's settled.
[One hand's just for support]
Thank you.
[Items currently owned]
[Team Lee Teuk]
[The gentleman over there sent it]
[Team Shin Dong]
[One hand's just for support]
[Final Round 3]
We'll begin Round 3.
[Team Lee Teuk: Lee Teuk VS
Team Shin Dong: DAWN]
Lee Teuk, I'm really sorry, but…
I don't think it'll be that hard.
Because he's slim. I'm slim too.
[Lee Teuk 61 kg vs DAWN 57 kg]
So, if Lee Teuk does it,
[A lightweight body with heavyweight confidence]
I thought I could win.
You seem confident about doing the plank.
Confident...
So, like, I'm confident against Lee Teuk.
When it comes to DAWN,
we all have this image in mind.
Weakling.
Toothpick.
Chopstick.
Thorn.
Anchovy.
I got the feeling
that I could beat him.
Oh, wait, wait!
[The weakling-thorn-anchovy
was waiting nearby]
This is great.
[Round 3: Battle of the prideful anchovies]
When you hear the whistle,
you must raise your knees.
[Which anchovy will win?]
Lee Teuk, your hips are a bit high.
Yeah, that's right.
[Feedback applied immediately]
Lee Teuk.
Huh? DAWN's hips are higher.
- They're similar right now.
- No, his are higher.
[A subtle hip-height standoff]
No, it's really similar.
[Subtly]
DAWN, you don't have to do that.
[Sincerely fine-tuning hip height]
Lee Teuk's hips are higher right now.
Oh, Lee Teuk...!
- Your hips were the highest!
- Right??
[Awkward]
Yeah, I apologize.
I shouldn't be calling anyone out.
[1 minute elapsed]
1 minute has passed.
Wow, they're being serious.
They're serious.
Their expressions right now…
Both of them are serious.
[It's a battle of the anchovies,
but Round 3 is carrying on smoothly]
Lee Teuk, you put
a ton of insoles in your shoes.
[Humiliation]
[Protect our brother]
They are really visible.
[Johnny protects Lee Teuk's pride]
That's actually a phone.
[With the top of
their heads even turning red]
[They break the dreaded 2-minute mark]
[2 minutes elapsed]
Okay, 2 minutes have passed.
They'll slowly start feeling it now.
Yeah, it hits hard right after 2 minutes.
Lee Teuk's really good at this.
But they're both really good.
- There's no wobbling.
- Seriously, no wobble.
[Meanwhile]
Lee Teuk is really not shaking at all.
[I'll show you that even anchovies are strong]
I'll prove skinny guys can be strong too.
Skinny sticks do burn well.
[Those two]
I think they're doing the best at this.
[Surprise main event: Lee Teuk VS DAWN]
- They're so chill. - They're the best at this.
So you need to be light for this.
- A little bit…
- It's coming, it's coming.
Oh, Lee Teuk!
It's here, it's here.
Lee Teuk's basically Cardi B right now.
[3 minutes elapsed]
3 minutes have passed.
Wow, they're really good.
[How did they hold on for 3 minutes?]
Wow, without even saying a word…!
Wow, they're both
really good at this.
It's here, it's here, it's here!
DAWN, you just need
to hold on a little longer!
- DAWN, you can win.
- For real.
[Both teams are hitting their limit]
He's feeling it, he's feeling it.
Lee Teuk's almost 50 soon.
You're gonna lose
to a 50-year-old?!
[Technically, he's 44 years old]
I'm 44.
- DAWN! This is the only thing you can do well!
- You, youngster!
You, youngster!
[Get it together]
If you lose here, you'll be a pauper forever.
You're trying to beat an old guy?
[Proving age is but a number, while trembling]
Hey kid, just take it easy.
Whatever you do…
[No answer]
[Anchovy DAWN's grind continues]
It was totally unexpected.
Rather than an anchovy,
[Acknowledging his eel power]
he felt more like an eel.
He's got serious strength.
[Respect from one anchovy to another]
He's one tough guy.
I was really surprised.
They're both really good.
I think they're gonna hit 4 minutes.
[4 minutes elapsed]
4 minutes have passed.
They're gonna hit 5 minutes.
[Hang in there a bit longer]
DAWN's really done.
- He's gone.
- Yeah, it's over.
[Side glance]
He's shaking a lot.
He dropped a lot.
[No way]
No, DAWN will continue like this
for like 10 minutes.
[Eel DAWN fights to hold on]
Oh, but…!
Your core! Your core!
Hold out with your core!
- That's right! DAWN, just a bit more!
- Hold out with your core.
Just hang in there a little longer.
[Who will win Round 3?]
Wow!
[Wobble]
- No!
- No, DAWN!
Can I do something with this?
[Use this at least]
DAWN, I'm sorry, but just a little more!
Go down.
DAWN, I'm sorry.
I'm really sorry about this.
DAWN, just a little longer.
[Shin Dong, I can't do it]
[Recorded 4 minutes and 30 seconds]
[Round 3 winner: Lee Teuk]
Lee Teuk!
Oh, Lee Teuk!
[This is what old-man strength looks like]
[A loss but an epic match]
It's all good, it's all good.
[So close]
We can do this well. It's fine, it's fine.
Wow.
The record holder for the longest time
of the "ALL or NOTHING" plank challenge!
- Yes.
- Lee Teuk!
[Traditional coin game]
Thank you.
[Team Lee Teuk grabs the final item]
The oldest person has the longest plank record.
He must work out pretty regularly…
- He really does.
- Right?
[Team Shin Dong starts with only 1 item]
Otherwise, there's no way he could do that
- Seriously impressive.
- Congratulations.
You're reserved to be paupers.
- Us?
- Yes.
[Trying to stay calm]
Just look at us. Who looks more like a pauper?
- Shin Dong, you're sweating buckets.
- Do I look too much like a pauper?
[You look the most like a pauper]
You look like a pauper.
Yes.
I think I'm gonna
be sore tomorrow.
I'm already sore…
[While clutching their sore abs...]
DAWN, doesn't it hurt here?
- It's here for me.
- Oh, it hurts there?
[Each team heads
to their assigned restaurant!]
[Feeling anxious]
We gotta get there faster than the other team...
But I suddenly
lost my confidence…
[Wait, what...]
We're here because we trusted you, though.
[You told us to trust you earlier...]
You can't suddenly do this to us.
[Trying to backtrack]
I'm suddenly sleepy. So strange.
[Must-have requirement]
Still, you two eat well, right?
[Eats well]
I do eat well.
[Not picky]
I'm not picky at all.
DAWN, you really eat a lot, right…?
[Extremely suspicious]
I'm really pretty good.
As long as it's not that. Lamb!
Oh, so there's
something you can't eat.
- Tell us what you can't eat.
- Anything fishy.
But Yo Han, since you did sports growing up,
you must've eaten a lot of things.
Yeah, if I didn't eat,
I used to get hit.
[Baby Yo Han grew up especially tough]
It was like that when we grew up. We got hit.
[Time for a strategy]
Which do you prefer, seafood and meat?
- Seafood for me!
- If you had to choose…Oh, seafood!
I'm not really into seafood.
Oh, I love seafood!
What about you?
[What about Yo Han?]
Seafood or meat?
- I basically eat whatever's given to me…
- Oh, then, okay! For you,
[In charge of big servings]
you eat a lot of both.
[In charge of the meat]
I'll eat a lot of the meat.
- You eat a lot of seafood.
- I'll eat lots of seafood.
[Tasks divided in a flash]
Okay.
I roughly looked up
healthy soul food online.
What did you find?
Beans!
Right? The beans here seem pretty famous.
- Lentils and stuff.
- Chickpeas.
[Just hearing it feels healthy]
Chickpeas came up a lot.
[Hmm...]
A soup made of…green leafy veggies…
Oh, I'm really good
at eating noodles.
Filajel...
Falafel?
Doesn't this seem healthy?
[Dubai Chewy Chocolate style]
A vegan menu.
Whatever it is,
[Mind says health; heart says national dish.]
we just have to eat it.
That's right.
I'm extremely hungry right now.
[Planning to win on hunger alone]
Our card is...
- just the hand-tying one, right?
- Yeah.
[Another meeting agenda: Attack items]
We gotta have a plan for this.
[Using attack items]
Rather than using them right away,
I think it's better
to save it for the end.
During Round 3.
[Agreeing]
- Round 3? - Because
at first, they're starving,
so they'll eat like crazy.
Like, they'll bring the food
close to their mouths to eat faster.
But later,
[Planning to attack when they're full]
in round 3, they'll be stuffed.
Or, since seafood
is hard to eat with a fork…
- Seafood is a good idea, Shin Dong!
- Right?
- Oh, seafood!
- You have to peel with your hands.
- You have to peel it!
- Right, right!
[Impressed]
Wow, Shin Dong, you're super strategic.
So, at that point…
[Smart]
Either during seafood or Round 3.
First, Shin Dong is seriously a strategist.
Shin Dong totally feels
like the brain of the team.
[Feeling safe with Strategist Shin Dong]
So, I was like, "Oh? This is so good."
[Deep in thought...]
From what I think,
as soon as it starts,
don't you think
they'll use the one-serving item?
[Helpless...]
[Preparing to eat 4 servings from the start]
We gotta just assume we're eating 4 servings.
But would they use
an item for healthy soul food?
[Is that right?]
Perhaps for larger portions?
I feel they'll use it
when we eat meat or something like that.
No, from what I see,
that team has no strategists.
All three of them
are just muscle power.
[While Team Shin Dong is
working hard on their strategy…]
Oh, right, we have to decide that.
After eating the first dish,
for the second dish…
We have to decide
if we're going with meat or fish.
[What?]
The order…
Isn't it already set?
- Like, which restaurant to go to…
- Oh, I didn't understand it.
[Reset]
So, it's decided?
[Still don't understand the rules]
You didn't know, right? Ji Sung?
[He's in the same boat]
I thought we had to decide.
- The order is fixed.
- Yeah.
- We have to decide what restaurant to go to.
- Right.
Aren't we deciding
if we're eating fish or meat?
[It's not that…]
There are two fish restaurants.
[Choose one of the two seafood spots,
or one of the two meat places]
That's right.
[You got it, right?]
Oh, okay! I get it now.
And right now,
[Team Shin Dong's attack item]
the one item we'll get
- is the hand-tying one.
- Yes.
I feel like they'll use it immediately…
It's actually better
if they use it for the start.
[If their hands are tied]
Like, if they use it when we're eating steak?
That'd be a disaster.
[The smartest of the bunch]
Because we have to cut it.
[Checking their items]
What do we have?
- The coin-flipping.
- The coin one.
- Add an extra serving.
[The attack items]
Or is it kinda lame to use them all at once...?
[So clever]
- During the meat one?
- All-in?
- Go all-in during the meat one?!
- Just go all-in during the meat one.
- That's a good idea.
- Going all-in is a good idea.
[A plan the guys totally dig]
They said earlier that
the Egyptian national dish is delicious.
But one thing I'm worried about is...
But it might only suit
Egyptian taste buds…
And another thing I'm curious about.
- They said it's "flavorful."
- Right.
- The exact flavor matters.
- Yeah, that's right.
- Is it spicy?
- Is it salty?
[Even sourness…]
- Is it sour or sweet? - Something like that.
[Drooling just thinking about it]
Something sour would be really hard.
- I like sour stuff.
- Oh, really?
[This is good]
Then you can just eat it all.
Don't people in hot places
usually eat a lot of spicy food?
But,
[Lee Teuk's prediction on spicy food]
if it's gonna be spicy,
[It won't be a national dish!]
it might not be a national dish.
[That actually sounds right]
Oh!
I think we need to look at
"flavorful" from a different angle.
[Pondering...]
But now that I think about it,
our production team is Korean…!
It's spicy...! We got them.
Johnny, you're a genius!
JohnnyUS...
[Moved]
Oh my god...
[With JohnnyUS]
We have to win this.
[Determined to be princes...]
We really need to be princes today…
The Nile River.
[Already reached the Nile River]
This is the Nile River.
There are definitely
more tall buildings by the river.
- There…
- There are lots of tall buildings.
[Exotic city vibes]
Oh! Over there, it's kind of like…
Oh, it's hitting me now.
It really feels like we're abroad.
Like we're in Egypt...
[Soaking up the rich vibes of Egypt…]
We're here, we're here.
[Arrived at the restaurant in no time]
Is this the place?
[The first restaurant
right in the heart of the city]
[An eco-friendly vibe,
as expected from a healthy food restaurant]
[Entering with good vibes]
This place has a nice atmosphere.
- It feels great.
- It's so classy.
I think the food's in there.
[Obviously, what they're about to eat]
That's definitely food
This smells good.
- I'm opening it.
- Okay.
[The appetizer that Team Shin Dong chose]
- First…
- What could it be?
- Is it warm?
- It's not warm.
[So, what is this healthy soul food?]
One, two, three!
- Wow!
- Huh?
It's that! The fried stuff!
It's that from earlier!
- The fried food we talked about earlier!
- Yeah, the one we saw earlier!
[The food they looked up in the car]
- We saw it. - Yeah, it's that!
[Fava beans]
[Cilantro]
[A batter made by blending various veggies]
[Shaped into little rounds]
[Tossed into hot oil]
[Egypt's signature vegan dish]
[Ta'ameya / Small portion]
[Enjoy]
- It smells great.
- Yeah, right?
I think it'll be yummy.
This kind of
feels like Egypt's version
of seasoned bean paste.
You wrap it in the bread
[Foul served with Ta'ameya]
and dip it in the sauce to eat together.
- Wrap it in the bread.
- Is this the bread?
[This is the bread…]
Is this the bread?
- You have to eat all the bread too.
- Oh, okay, okay.
[Eish: A word meaning life or survival]
Wrap it in the bread…
[Finish everything,
including the eish, to win]
Oh, okay. Alright.
So, you put this here,
and do it like this.
[The perfect trio for an epic bite]
This one…
Oh, but I think
this is gonna be delicious.
In that case,
I think we need to divide it a little.
Yeah.
Let's just eat it quickly first.
[Shut your mouth and eat]
Sorry, but just zip it and eat.
[A mission where
they must quickly enjoy the food]
- Is it okay?
Mmm!
- It's good! It's tasty!
- It's good?
[Quickly taking a bite after Shin Dong]
- DAWN might struggle a bit with it.
- Mmm!
It has a subtle hint of spices to it.
But it's delicious.
- It's a spice that I like.
- Oh, really?
Totally. This is really delicious.
This is really my kind of flavor.
I want to eat this so badly.
I'm losing my mind.
[Trembling]
Oh, this is…
It's kind of like
a Korean-style meat patty.
- It's that kind of vibe.
- Yeah, it has that vibe. Right.
[Touched]
- Mmm! - It's really tasty.
[All three are totally satisfied]
I think we made the right choice.
We picked well, we picked well.
[Unlimited drinks]
Nice.
Thank you.
But there's no meat in this?
There's no meat.
All beans and no meat.
[The inside is green]
That's why it's green on the inside.
[Stuffed with various veggies]
Oh, you're right.
They're bean fritters. Bean fritters.
- But it kinda tastes like meat.
- I know, right?
It's so good.
I don't know what to do.
[Ta'ameya totally hits the spot]
Hey, we really eat well.
I think I picked well.
[Totally agree]
For real.
- Right?
- Totally.
[F.N.D]
I think Team Lee Teuk's gonna get a lot of food.
[Team Lee Teuk]
Let's go, let's go!
[Appetizer]
It's here, it's here.
- Wow, that looks good.
- I'm starving.
[Team Lee Teuk arrives at the first restaurant]
It looks tasty.
[The restaurant's packed with customers]
Wow, it's already crowded.
There are a lot of customers.
[Right in the heart of Cairo, Egypt]
[Taking over the entire building
with the national dish]
[A famous restaurant loved by the locals]
Oh, man.
[Seats are on the 5th floor]
Oh, wow.
- Why is it so high up?
- Oh, man.
[Getting even hungrier]
Shouldn't we eat quickly?
Lee Teuk. Don't take your time.
[The eldest is innocent]
I wasn't taking my time.
There are so many awards here.
But, Lee Teuk, should we catch our breath?
Or just go straight in?
[Catching your breath now is a luxury]
Let's go right away. Sit down.
We don't have time.
[Team Lee Teuk's first dish is?]
Now, our first dish!
[A flavorful national dish]
A flavorful…
- National dish.
[Excited]
Let's open it.
One, two, three!
[A first for Egyptian food]
[UNESCO Intangible Cultural Heritage]
[Tossing pasta and rice in one bowl]
[Whoosh]
[Drizzling on the magical sauce]
[+ garlic flakes]
[+ chickpeas]
[A flavor combo
that simply cannot taste bad]
[Koshari / Big portion]
- Number 1.
[A Koshari guide appears]
Lee Teuk, we have
to follow along right away.
[We have no time to wait]
[Lemon + garlic vinegar + salt + spicy sauce]
Garlic sauce.
[Blending 4 ingredients for the sauce]
Spicy.
[Lastly]
Tomato sauce.
[A familiar dish with pasta vibes]
It's like a pasta dish!
And onions.
[Add toppings to your taste]
Onion, onion.
Mix together.
[Shake, shake, shake]
Wow.
[Try this Egyptian F.N.D]
Good?
[The guide clocks out]
- Whoa, that's interesting.
- So, how is it? How is it?
[Curious, but cautious]
Honestly, what do you think? Be honest.
Oh, I got it.
It's like a mix of
pasta, cereal, and rice.
[What even is that...]
Pasta, cereal, rice?
Yeah. You're right.
- There's rice and pasta in here together.
- There's rice?
[Rice grains, pasta noodles]
This is interesting.
[Taking a bite of the fascinating combo]
Whoa!!
It's spicy.
[But it's good!!]
It's delicious.
It's good.
How is it?
Adding spicy sauce
definitely kicks it up a notch.
Pass me the spicy sauce.
[Zero hesitation when curiosity strikes]
[Sniff, sniff]
So, this is basically like…
Whoa!
- It's really spicy, huh?
- Wow, it's hot!
Hey, that's way too spicy!
But…
It's not the kind of
spiciness you find in Korea.
I guess the chili fragrance
is a bit different?
- It's Tabasco sauce, but the spicy kind.
- Exactly.
It reminds me of spaghetti
[Egypt's true national dish, Koshari]
served at school back in the day,
but a multigrain version.
If you came here just to travel,
would you come here again?
I feel like I'd definitely eat this again.
[A true national favorite]
Not many people would dislike this.
- For sure, definitely.
- Yeah.
Everyone,
[You haven't forgotten the rules, right…?]
don't forget this is a game of speed.
[Lightning-fast reactions]
But I bet they arrived before us.
- Yeah.
- Looking at the map.
[Mystery]
What if the other team already ate and left?
[Did they already eat and go?]
I know, right?
[Team Shin Dong's still eating]
- I could keep eating this.
- This is totally
a breeze, right?
If it's like this.
I'm curious about this too.
What is this?
[Spotted salt & pepper in front of them]
What is this? Is it salt?
Pepper? What is it?
It just tastes salty.
- Salt?
- I think it's salt. S…
Oh, salt isn't "S".
[Salt is S(alt)]
S… Hey.
Yo Han just said…
[Shin Dong, please]
Yo Han asked what it was,
and then said,
"S? S, salt?"
[We got it either way]
[Salt is Sogeum]
Sure.
Then what's this? P?
- That's "Puchu".
- "Puchu".
Right, "puchu".
[Feeling reassured]
But I feel like
you guys eat slowly?
I already ate two.
This is my third one.
- You're already on your third?
- Yes.
- You're on your third?
- Yeah.
[Yo Han met his quota]
Then I should eat three too.
[Team Shin Dong picks up the speed]
[Enjoying a full-course
dining experience in Cairo]
[The irony of rushing through a delicious meal]
[The golden youngest stands out]
Ji Sung, you really eat fast.
[Way slower in contrast is]
[The oldest bro's chewing]
But I think I'll be full just eating this.
[Glancing over]
Sorry, okay...
[Lee Teuk, you're not gonna be a prince??]
That glare was intense.
If Team Shin Dong
took the extra serving item,
[Quite a big portion]
eating this would've been hard.
- It would've been hard.
- Yeah, pretty brutal.
Should we pick up the pace now?
- Just you, Lee Teuk.
- Oh, sorry.
I really want to
sleep as a prince today.
Seriously, as a prince today.
[The Pharaoh's Table with a total of 4 rounds]
[The team that races through
the fastest becomes princes]
[Who'll win the appetizer round?]
I think I finished my share.
- We ate it all.
- I had three.
[Team Shin Dong finishes their meal]
That was delicious.
Wow, that was so good.
[Completely polished off the plates]
Yes, you finished it all.
[Team Shin Dong clears the appetizers]
- Totally successful!
- Hey, our team is solid.
[Smug]
The next stop is for fish.
[Second course]
[Time to pick the seafood dish]
- You've got two options.
- Yeah.
- Here's the keyword.
[Curious]
Number 1.
Number 1. A dish that appears in Egyptian murals.
[A. A dish seen in Egyptian murals]
It's even in the murals?
- And?
- Number 2.
[B. An expensive dish in Korea, too]
An expensive dish in Korea, too.
[Strategist Shin Dong's brain activates]
Numbers 1 and 2 are different, right?
Yeah, they're different.
For the Egyptian mural food,
I had a feeling
the fish would come out whole.
These people didn't
just paint dishes on the murals.
They would paint
the fish shape on the murals.
So, I thought it'd be
difficult to finish everything cleanly.
[Let's avoid the Egyptian mural dish for now]
Rather than the mural food,
it's better to choose something else.
Gourmet dishes come in small portions.
For expensive dishes,
[Fine dining is a one-bite affair - Shin Dong]
the portion is this tiny.
We can just eat a big spoonful and go.
[Brain power off]
Okay, hear me out.
"A" sounds like the portion size will be big.
"B" is pricey,
so it'll probably have a smaller portion.
[Adding his two cents]
In my opinion,
In my opinion, for "A",
if it's in the Egyptian murals,
- then it's probably an Egyptian traditional dish.
- Right.
- It could be a hit or miss.
I'm kind of
- leaning towards "B".
- I'm also actually
[Yo Han & Shin Dong lean toward B...]
leaning towards "B". What about you?
- Oh, really,?
- You're leaning towards "A"?
I'm kind of scared…
[What could the expensive ingredient be?]
Since it's a pricey ingredient.
It could be something like caviar.
If that's the vibe,
that's not bad at all.
Right? Actually,
we can just close our eyes,
- Right.
- take a bit, and it's over.
- And it could actually be really yummy.
- Yeah.
- Shall we go with "B"?
- Let's go with "B".
[Just trust my instincts]
Let's do "B", let's do "B".
Our choice is
"B"!
[B. An expensive dish in Korea too]
We'll mark it on the map and show you.
[Location is key]
Oh, right, there's a map.
No, either way,
[Distance is pure luck anyway]
we wouldn't know about the distance.
[Anxious]
[Getting nervous
after making a quick choice]
[Revealing the map]
[Where is the restaurant
Team Shin Dong chose?]
[Meanwhile]
[Team Lee Teuk's
Koshari attack has slowed down]
It gets spicier the more you eat.
It might be because
it's been sitting too long.
[Just then, Shin Dong calls to check in]
Oh, Shin Dong?
- Hello?
- Hey, Lee Teuk!
- Yeah.
- You must still be eating.
[Yes, they are still eating]
Nah, we're all done.
[No, that's a lie]
You're still eating?
We finished eating.
[Getting a weird vibe]
We left for our second spot a while ago.
Oh, congratulations.
[The spoon moves more urgently]
Oh no, what are you gonna do?
Was the food pretty good?
You didn't get
the second keyword yet, huh?
[The second... keyword?]
Yeah.
We haven't seen…
We're still eating.
[Confessed before
they could even get caught]
[Oh dear]
We'll head out first, then!
Have a good trip.
[Team Lee Teuk is in trouble]
We're in trouble.
This is bad.
I'm way too slow! What do we do?
[No way we're gonna lose]
Can I take some?
[The youngest assists for a comeback]
I actually… eat faster than expected.
I need to take charge... of this surgery…!
Of this game!
[I'll be the lead surgeon of this game…!]
It's so spicy!
It's so intense!
[Team Lee Teuk works harder]
I'm gonna be a prince today.
[Then, where is
the restaurant Team Shin Dong picked?]
[Nervous]
Where is it?
- Is it the place with the X?
- Oh, it's the farthest!
[Bust]
[They picked the farthest restaurant!]
It's the farthest place.
[Anxious, they spy on the other team]
Hey Lee Teuk.
[You didn't get the second keyword yet, huh?]
Yeah.
[They're still eating…!]
They're eating! They're eating!
I can hear them
wiping their mouths so clearly.
Right? They're still chewing!
Enjoy your meal.
We'll head out first, then!
- Have a good trip.
- They're eating.
He was like, "Have a good trip!"
Okay, let's go.
We're in the lead for now.
- We said the portions would be big.
- Their portions must be big.
Their portions are big.
[In a hurry]
Let's go!
Oh, I ate so well.
- I really ate so well.
- It was so good.
[Team Shin Dong]
[Appetizer: Clear]
At this rate, I think we can win.
[Team Shin Dong]
[Off to the second course first]
[Feeling stuck]
But it's getting spicier the more I eat it.
[Super T-type]
I think you just poured too much sauce.
[Pacing nervously]
[Cola SOS]
But won't drinking cola fill us up?
- Right? That's what I'm worried about.
- Right?
But we can't help but drink it.
[Johnny clears his plate first]
It's really good.
Let's go.
[The eldest pushes through to the end]
[Go first]
Move, move!
We gotta hurry and go.
[We're done,
so give us the keyword too]
Team Lee Teuk,
here's your seafood keyword.
[A. A dish that appears in Egyptian murals]
"B."
[B. An expensive dish in Korea, too]
There's a similar dish in Korea?
You need to understand it right away.
We've got no time to waste.
Let's eat the similar dish.
- The similar one?
- Yeah.
Is it similar or expensive?
Expensive.
- Oh, something expensive.
- What's better?
We came all this way,
so the Egyptian mural dish…
Right? Let's keep the romance alive.
[The romantic trip ignites once more]
I was gonna choose that, too.
- "A."
- You're choosing "A"?
[A. A dish that appears in Egyptian murals]
The dish that appears in paintings.
[Quick decision]
[Missed Team Shin Dong again]
I hope it's something like clams.
[Before Team Lee Teuk picks a restaurant]
Here's the current scoreboard.
- Wow, that's far.
- They went all the way there?
[A new X is added]
We have to go that far?
This is the current situation.
[Team Shin Dong is currently en route]
We haven't updated it yet.
Does "X" mean it's done?
It's the place that was chosen.
Huh? Oh!
That means Team B went there!
They went, or it's similar to us…
But for us,
[Team Lee Teuk's destination is still a secret]
we don't know if it's here, here, or here.
Alright, now then,
with the place you've chosen,
[Finally revealing Team Lee Teuk's location]
we'll update the map now.
[The one who doesn't get the game]
A dish that appears in Egyptian murals.
[The one who gets the game]
We're good. It's somewhere close, Lee Teuk.
[The one who just likes the game]
It's somewhere close.
[What fate awaits Team Lee Teuk?!]
We're good, we're good!
Let's go, let's go!
[The seafood course picked by Team Lee Teuk]
The owner's gonna be surprised.
[Team Shin Dong left first,
but is headed to the outskirts of the city]
[Team Lee Teuk is lagging,
but chose a closer location]
[The direction of the game
becomes totally unpredictable again]
Let's go!
[Appetizers: CLEAR]
Go, go! Move, move!
It feels like a speed-eating challenge.
Food fighters!
I wonder if the other team
finished eating and headed out.
We'll definitely arrive first.
They were still eating
when we called after we were done.
Hey, let's think this through.
- We're on our second course.
- Yes.
They have
two attack items right now.
But we didn't get any attacks
at the first restaurant.
Wanna play Rock-Paper-Scissors?
[Another twist to the game]
Rock-Paper-Scissors!
[Attack items]
[Team Lee Teuk's Item 1]
[Acquired "Add an extra serving"]
Go down.
[Team Lee Teuk's Item 2]
[Acquired "Coin-flipping"]
But when we use ours,
should we use it on
seafood or meat?
[And the round that
Yo Han won with great difficulty]
Johnny, remember
those tough trainee days of yours.
[Team-Kill]
[Team Shin Dong's Item 1]
[Acquired "Tied hands"]
We'll go with the hand-tying one.
Huh?
[Team Shin Dong only has 1 attack item]
So for Rounds 2 and 3, they'll definitely…
- Use them.
- They'll definitely use them, right?
[Team Lee Teuk holds 2 attack items]
Let's go all-in for Round 3.
Yeah, during Round 3.
When this show ends,
we'll either leave super close,
or feud-ridden.
It'll be one of the two.
Actually, Johnny…
If there's something
Ji Sung and I can't eat,
you have to eat it for us.
Because… Hear me out.
Ji Sung and I won our matches.
- But you lost yours.
- Oh!
But that kind of makes sense…!
[Right?!]
Yeah, it does, right?
[The team's lone strategist becomes the target]
We need our own set of rules.
Today,
- Today, we're gonna lose.
- No, no, no.
You have to do it for us.
You're our team's ace!
An ace who loses?
But if we become paupers,
exactly how poor are we gonna be?
Like, super poor?!
[Extreme]
Like, no phones allowed…
They wouldn't
actually take our phones, right?
[Not that extreme]
We'll give you phones.
And then, the paupers
have to go to the king's house
and pay their respects, right?
[Wow, that's a great idea?]
- Pay their respects…
- Hey, don't say things like that.
[The staff wasn't even thinking about that…]
The production team didn't even consider that.
When you watch
dating reality shows,
some people never
even make it to paradise.
All-paupers.
- Pauper all the way.
But that could be better.
Going from prince to pauper
would be so brutal!
But if you keep living as a pauper,
you'll be like, "Oh, so this is how it is!"
Then, let's be paupers today.
[Startled]
No, no.
[The reliable big brother who goes back and forth]
Lee Teuk is so inconsistent!
Johnny.
Rather than that,
let's just keep winning.
[Real talk]
I don't think I can be a pauper…
But even if I become a pauper,
it would seem weird.
A chubby pauper is just strange.
[A well-fed pauper is odd to everyone]
Isn't a well-fed pauper kind of weird?
[Resolution]
I guess we have to be princes then.
We've gone a bit out now.
[Team Shin Dong slowly eases into the outskirts]
Yeah, we left the city quickly.
Wow! This place…!
It's got night market vibes!
[In awe]
Wow!
This place is amazing!
[Endless rows of street shops
unfold outside the window]
This kinda reminds me of…
- Dongmyo style?
- Yeah.
- There's no end.
- Wow!
Wow, this is amazing.
Oh, they said it's a market.
Wow!!!
This place is seriously incredible!
[Amazed]
Wow!
Wow, it's really
densely populated here.
Cairo alone has
about 20 million people.
Really?
Then again, Egypt is like
10 times the size of Korea…
This must be a fabric market!
There are tons of fabrics.
[True to Egypt's fame for cotton,
the fabric market is bustling]
If we become princes, do we get to wear
traditional clothes and do this kind of thing?
I wanna try
wearing it at least once.
I think it'd be super comfy.
[That wish will come true one day]
[Heart flutter]
[This time, Lee Teuk makes a spy call]
Lee Teuk is calling, everyone.
They must've finished eating.
Yes, hello?
Did you enjoy your meal?
You just finished it now?!
We got like a giant bowl of food.
[LOL]
Shin Dong, you predicted correctly!
[I am Strategist Shin Dong]
I predicted it exactly.
Lee Teuk, what did you pick
for the second course?
[Shin Dong] Did you pick "A" or "B"?
Oh, they picked "A."
I still don't
understand that part.
Oh, you picked "A?"
Yeah, you picked "B," huh?
Yes, we picked "B."
[Lee Teuk]
Oh my...
[Testing the waters]
"A" seemed to be in a really far place.
[Not buying it]
"A" is actually closer.
No, "A" was really far away.
[Confident]
We're almost there already, though?
[Surprised]
Already?
You're right.
We just need to cross one bridge.
[Revealing true feelings]
Oh…We're in trouble.
Okay, Lee Teuk.
[The tables turn in an instant]
The tables turned immediately.
I heard it takes you
40 minutes to get there.
We finished our second course
[Bluffing]
and are headed to our third one.
Oh, really?
[An endless cycle of deception]
Our extra serving is headed your way soon.
Oh, yes, thank you so much.
Yes, sir.
Oh, we're in trouble…
Team Lee Teuk's spot is closer.
This is what I was worried about…
Should we use the item now?!
- No.
- Let's use it for Round 3.
We're going all the way to the right side now.
If we pick wrong next time
and end up all the way on the left…
We'll lose for sure.
[Guaranteed to be paupers]
That will be really…
We're reading each other's moves.
We totally know
each other inside out.
I feel like we're almost there.
Hey, we must be
going somewhere nice.
This place has
something like a Han River view.
Nile River view.
[Embracing thousands of years]
Wow, this place is stunning!
[A restaurant by the Nile River]
It has that Han River vibe
you mentioned earlier!
[Found the hint]
Yeah, total Han River vibes.
Oh! It might be
on the murals here.
[Egyptian murals displayed at the entrance]
The Egyptian murals are drawn here like this.
Since it's a seafood spot…
Assalamu alaikum!
Wow!!
The view is amazing!
The view is seriously so nice!
[Where your eyes and palate
are charmed at the same time]
This is nice.
Oh? It's just one! What a relief!
Hey, there's definitely lemon.
- Okay, shall we begin?
- We're jumping right in! Here we go!
- Open, open, open! Let's go!
- One, two, three!
- Oh!
- Okay, okay!
[A little luxury spread out on the table]
[Freshness that
embodies the deep blue Red Sea]
[Paired with fresh veggies and seasoning]
[Grilled over a strong fire]
[Grouper]
[Known as the "Beef of the Sea",
a grouper-family fish with firm, savory meat]
[Grouper / Just the right amount]
- This seriously looks good!
- It looks so good! It looks so good!
Okay!
First…!
[A quick check for bones]
[Taking it all in]
But like…this place is nice.
[High expectations]
This looks so delicious.
Ji Sung, here.
[The eldest takes care of the youngest first]
The meat, the meat.
Thank you.
How is it?
It's really good!
It's really good?
It kind of reminds me of
something I had in China.
It has a bit of a smoky flavor!
[Nom]
There are so many flavors.
Yeah, it's like…
Have you tried
pepper crab in Singapore before?
[Pepper crab]
Oh yeah, it's seriously yummy.
It has that kind of vibe.
[A crab dish with a mix of spices
and black pepper]
This is good.
- So good.
- So good. It's really good.
[Safe to say the food is good,
judging from how fast they're digging in]
So, this is what's
on the Egyptian murals.
We picked well for this one…!
[Peak satisfaction]
This is so good.
- I like the peppery part of it.
- Right?
The pepper taste is…
So you like pepper too?
I think it has
curry powder and turmeric.
- It does, right?
- Yeah.
Huh? Who…are you?!?!
[What's happening…?]
[A dark figure silently creeps in]
Oh, you scared me…!
[Bewildered eyes]
[And the suspicious item
in the suspicious person's hand]
[Please]
[Give me your hands]
[Attack item]
[Team Shin Dong used it…!]
What if they feed each other?
[Excited just imagining it]
Like, their hands are tied.
They'll purposely push it around,
like, "You eat it."
[Used an attack item at the right timing]
I think they'll drop it all.
Lee Teuk, you don't
have to tie your hands, right?
Since we're on this side?
[Why...?]
Am I getting tied too?
[Obviously]
[Oh...]
I somehow ended up in the middle.
[Bring it over]
Should we do it like this?
[They keep trying to start a conversation, but…]
Isn't this something we should decide?
Did you talk about
how to tie us together?
[Just doing it because it's work]
[The person in black is quite shy]
Ji Sung.
You just stay seated.
[The meal resumes
in a rather rude posture]
But Lee Teuk, don't you think
it's so romantic right now?
Our Ji Sung, open wide!
[The night deepens in Cairo]
[With the race getting an upgrade]
[The vibe changes 180 degrees?!]
Eat faster!
[If all they did so far was eat…]
[Get it together]
This is driving me crazy.
[The mind games will begin now]
[With rampant interference]
Lee Teuk, can you please wait for us?
We're gonna take a while.
[And growing suspicion]
I don't think I can trust them!
Hey, we told you
everything so honestly.
[The endless]
We're gonna use our item.
[The endless sabotage attempts]
Why are you sending so many missions?
[The pauper life inches closer]
Oh no, this is bad. Wait.
[Those who want to be princes]
We're in big trouble.
Let's go!
Compared to coming from here,
we're way faster.
- Right? Way faster, for sure.
- Go faster!
[However, never let your guard down]
Why is the traffic so bad?
Don't let your guard down.
[Until the very end, there's no way of knowing]
I'm nervous. Aren't you nervous?
I honestly thought we'd win.
[The results of this race of false hope!]
It keeps giving me hope until the end.
[For the paupers who lost the race]
This can't be real.
[The world's only desert suite…]
Are reality shows usually this hard?
[Who will be the winners of this fate?]
[And… "ALL or NOTHING" leaves Cairo]
Wow, this is amazing.
[What's the next destination?]
This is what travel's all about.
[Doubling the desire to win]
[A luxury cruise fit for a prince]
Oh, it's here!
Wow, this is so romantic!
[What's the next mission
that'll unfold in this romantic new city?]